Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos (Box 1)
  - Uncommon Knowledge
    - Level Paying Field: Campaign Finance Reform, 00-1182 (Box 103)
    - Russian to Judgment: Russia After USSR, 00-1183 (Box 103)
    - Fear of International Trying: The International Criminal Court, 00-1184 (Box 103)
    - Don't It Make My Brown Eyes Blue: Ethics of Human Genetic Engineering, 00-1185 (Box 103)
    - Trading On Our Fears: The World Trade Organization, 00-1186 (Box 103)
    - A Tale of Two Chinas: The Future of Taiwan, 00-1187 (Box 103)
    - Working Hard or Hardly Working? Living Wage Ordinances, 00-1188 (Box 103)
    - No Nukes is Good Nukes: Nuclear Nonproliferation, 00-1189 (Box 103)
    - Sales of a Death Plan: Capital Punishment, 00-1190 (Box 103)
    - Milton Friedman on the New Economy, 00-1191 (Box 103)
    - MILTON'S PARADISE GAINED: MILTON FRIEDMAN'S ADVICE fOR THE NEXT PRESIDENT, 00-1192 (Box 103)
    - That '70s Show: The Meaning of the 1970s, 00-1193 (Box 103)
    - Terms of Endowment: Government Funding of the Arts, 00-1194 (Box 103)
    - Primary Colors: The Presidential Primary System, 00-1195 (Box 103)
    - The Wedding Zinger: The Definition of Marriage, 00-1196 (Box 103)
    - For Whom The Bell Tolls: The Spanish Civil War, 00-1197 (Box 103)
    - The Ravaged Century: A Look Back at the Twentieth Century, 00-1198 (Box 103)
    - Terms of Endowment: Government Funding of the Arts, 00-1199 (Box 103)
    - The Thin Blue Line: United Nations Peacekeeping Missions, 01-1113 (Box 104)
    - See Johnny Click: Computers in Education, 01-1114 (Box 104)
    - Smoke Gets In Your Eyes: The EPA and Cost-Benefit Analysis, 01-1115 (Box 104)
    - Si, Change: Mexico Transforming, 01-1116 (Box 104)
    - Lost for Words: Politics and the English Language, 01-1117 (Box 104)
    - So Sue Me: Tort Reform, 01-1118 (Box 104)
    - On the American Plan: American Foreign Policy, 01-1119 (Box 104)
    - NMD on Target? National Missile Defense, 01-1120 (Box 104)
    - Bye Bye Bilingual: Bilingual Education, 01-1121 (Box 104)
    - Power to the People: Electricity Deregulation, 01-1122 (Box 104)
    - Pay it Backwards: The Federal Budget Surplus, 01-1123 (Box 104)
    - Taking the Initiative: The Initiative Process, 01-1124 (Box 104)
    - The High and the Mighty: The War on Drugs, 01-1125 (Box 104)
    - Emission Impossible: Implementing the Kyoto Protocal, 01-1126 (Box 104)
    - Disharmony of the Spheres: Science and Religion, 01-1127 (Box 104)
    - Exorcizing the Vote: Voting Reform, 01-1128 (Box 104)
    - Hippocrates Call Your Office: Biomedical Ethics, 01-1129 (Box 104)
    - Death & Taxes: The Estate Tax, 01-1130 (Box 104)
    - The World at (Trade) War, 01-1131 (Box 104)
    - Under the Skin: Shelby Steele on Race in America, 01-1132 (Box 104)
    - Globalization and It's Discontents: The Impact of Globalization, 01-1133 (Box 104)
    - Putting the SAT to the Test: The SAT and College Admissions, 01-1134 (Box 104)
    - O' Big Brother, Where Art Thou?: The Regulation of Cyberspace, 01-1135 (Box 104)
    - Making a Federalist Case: Federalism and the Supreme Court, 01-1136 (Box 104)
  - Teachers on Teaching
    - On Creative Thinking, 95-1201 (Box 105)
    - On Encouraging Diversity in the Classroom, 95-1202 (Box 105)
    - Getting Inside Your Students' Heads, 96-1204 (Box 105)
    - Relating To Your Students, 96-1205 (Box 105)
    - Galvanizing the Student Muse: Creative Work in an Academic Setting, 96-1206 (Box 105)
    - Teaching Through Problem Solving: Perspectives After Eighteen Years in the Trenches, 96-1207 (Box 105)
    - Seven Habits of Highly Effective Teachers, 96-1208 (Box 105)
    - Dealing with an Eclectic Audience, 96-1209 (Box 105)
    - Controversy and Social Commitment in the Classroom, 96-1210 (Box 105)
    - Leading Discussions, 97-1211 (Box 105)
    - How to Give a Lecture, 97-1212 (Box 105)
    - Creating Links Between Technology and Teaching, 97-1213 (Box 106)
    - How to Design and Teach a New Course, 97-1214 (Box 106)
    - Bringing Community Service into the Classroom, 97-1215 (Box 106)
    - A Learning Tool: The Student-Produced Video as a Coursework Option, 97-1216 (Box 106)
    - Introductory Economic Studies: Some Teaching and Learning Ideas, 97-1217 (Box 106)
    - Learning Through Teaching, 97-1218 (Box 106)
    - Cultivating the Capacity for Rigorous Critical Analysis: A Vital Pedagogical Task, 98-1219 (Box 106)
    - Incorporating New Technologies into the Teaching Process, 98-1220 (Box 106)
    - Designing the Exam: Necessary Evil or Opportunity, 98-1221 (Box 106)
    - Classroom Burn-Out: Experiencing It, Dealing With It, and Learning From It, 98-1223 (Box 106)
    - Seeing the Forest Through the Trees: Vertical Learning and Teaching Science, 98-1222 (Box 106)
    - Teaching American Foreign Policy, 98-1224 (Box 107)
    - Being a Machine vs. Being Curious: What Do Students Want?, 98-1225 (Box 107)
    - Teaching Introductory Probability: Sharing My Experience to Create the Urge to Know, 98-1226 (Box 107)
    - Letting Them Do It Themselves - In Small Groups, 98-1227 (Box 107)
    - Student-Friendly Lecturing, 99-1228 (Box 107)
    - What I Learned About Teaching and Learning in Sophomore College, 99-1229 (Box 107)
    - Preparing for Your Future Academic Career, 99-1230 (Box 107)
    - How to Have a Good Class Discussion, 99-1231 (Box 107)
    - Teaching Across the Disciplines, 99-1232 (Box 107)
    - Some Tricks of the Trade: Connecting With Your Students, 99-1233 (Box 107)
    - Teaching as Learning: The Process of Designing a New Course, 99-1234 (Box 107)
    - Questions and Admissions: Reflections on 100,000 Admissions Decisions at Stanford, 95-1301 (Box 108)
    - How To Give an Academic Job Talk, 00-1236 (Box 108)
    - Snap, Crackle and Pop: The Value of the Laboratory Experience in the Sciences, 00-1237 (Box 108)
    - Soap Bubbles, Thermodynamics and Engineering Science: Teaching the Ideas behind all the Mathematics", 00-1238 (Box 108)
    - Back to the Basics: Presenting the Foundations of One's Discipline, 00-1239 (Box 108)
    - Image isn't everything, but in teaching fluid mechanics it sure helps!, 00-1241 (Box 108)
    - History Wired: Technology Enhanced Teaching, 00-1242 (Box 108)
    - Reflections on the Experience of Team Teaching, 01-1243 (Box 108)
    - Teaching Strategies for Case-based Learning: Environmental Problems in the Classroom, 01-1244 (Box 108)
    - Analyzing the Complex Task of Teaching, 99-1235 (Box 108)
    - Teaching by the Case Method, 00-1240 (Box 108)
  - Stanford Authors
    - Learned Hand: The Man and the Judge, 95-1302 (Box 109)
    - Germany Unified and Europe Transformed: A Study in Statecraft, 95-1303 (Box 109)
    - The Orangery, 95-1304 (Box 109)
    - On Our Own Terms: Portraits of Women Business Leaders, 95-1305 (Box 109)
    - Celebrating 50 Years of Creative Writing at Stanford, 96-1306 (Box 109)
    - An Origin Like Water, 96-1307 (Box 109)
    - America Is Me, 96-1308 (Box 109)
    - Bringing Design to Software, 96-1309 (Box 109)
    - Caballero: An Historical Novel, 96-1310 (Box 109)
    - The Handmaid of Desire, 96-1311 (Box 109)
    - Lying on the Couch, 96-1312 (Box 109)
    - Betrayal of Science and Reason, 96-1313 (Box 110)
    - The Coming White Minority, 96-1314 (Box 110)
    - The Media Equation: How People Treat Computers, Television and New Media Like Real People and Places, 96-1315 (Box 110)
    - Marx Deceased, 96-1316 (Box 110)
    - Morning Glory, Evening Shadow, 97-1317 (Box 110)
    - History of the Breast, 97-1318 (Box 110)
    - This Is The Place, 97-1319 (Box 110)
    - Jealous Hearted Me, 97-1320 (Box 110)
    - Ear to the Ground, 97-1321 (Box 110)
    - Daybreak of Freedom, 97-1322 (Box 110)
    - Right Mind: Making Sense of the Hemispheres, 97-1323 (Box 110)
    - Taking Hold of the Torah: Jewish Commitment and Community, 97-1324 (Box 111)
    - Making More Waves: New Writing by Asian American Women, 98-1325 (Box 111)
    - Killing the Black Body: Race, Reproduction and the Meaning of Liberty, 98-1326 (Box 111)
    - Assignment Rescue: An Autobiography by Varian Fry, 98-1327 (Box 111)
    - Contemporary Europe and the Atlantic Alliance, 98-1328 (Box 111)
    - A Knock at Midnight: Inspiration from the Great Sermons of Reverend Martin Luther King, Jr., 98-1329 (Box 111)
    - The Student Body, 98-1330 (Box 111)
    - In the Stream of History: Shaping Foreign Policy for a New Era, 98-1331 (Box 111)
    - The Fast Track, 98-1332 (Box 111)
    - Hunger, 98-1333 (Box 111)
    - Share Our Strengths: The 1998 Writers' Harvest, 98-1334 (Box 111)
    - Blood of the Liberals, 00-1335 (Box 112)
    - Moving Lessons: Margaret H'Doubler and the Beginnng of Dance in American Education, 00-1336 (Box 112)
    - The 10-Second Internet Manager, 00-1337 (Box 112)
    - Labor Relations: Law, Politics and the NLRB, 00-1338 (Box 112)
    - Sustaining the New Economy, 00-1339 (Box 112)
    - The Dynamics of Global Dominance, 01-1340 (Box 112)
    - NATO: Its Past, Present and Future, 01-1341 (Box 112)
  - Legal Issues in Cyberspace
    - Introduction to Cyberspace, Program #1, 97-1509 (Box 112)
    - The Zoning of Cyberspace: Legal and Technological Approaches to the Regulation of Online Content, Program #2 tape #1, 97-1510 (Box 112)
    - The Zoning of Cyberspace: Legal and Technological Approaches to the Regulation of Online Content, Program #2 tape #2, 97-1510 (Box 112)
    - Encryption: Technological Savior or Recipe for Anarchy? Program #3 tape #1, 97-1511 (Box 112)
    - Encryption: Technological Savior or Recipe for Anarchy? Program #3 tape #2, 97-1511 (Box 112)
    - Copyright I: Maximalists, Minimalists, Framers and Linkers, Program #4 tape #1, 97-1512 (Box 112)
    - Copyright I: Maximalists, Minimalists, Framers and Linkers, Program #4 tape #2, 97-1512 (Box 112)
    - Copyright II: Copyright Enforcement Technologies- The New Economics of Intellectual Property, Program #5 tape #1, 97-1513 (Box 113)
    - Copyright II: Copyright Enforcement Technologies- The New Economics of Intellectual Property, Program #5 tape #2, 97-1513 (Box 113)
    - Success and Failure in Electronic Commerce: Business Models and Online Advertising, Program #6 tape #1, 97-1514 (Box 113)
    - Success and Failure in Electronic Commerce: Business Models and Online Advertising, Program #6 tape #2, 97-1514 (Box 113)
    - Creating an Electronic Commerce Ecosystem: Digital Cash and Payment Systems, Program #7 tape #1, 97-1515 (Box 113)
    - Creating an Electronic Commerce Ecosystem: Digital Cash and Payment Systems, Program #7 tape #2, 97-1515 (Box 113)
    - Re-thinking Minimum Contacts: The Problem of Jurisprudence and Choice of Law in Cyberspace, Program #8 tape #1, 97-1516 (Box 113)
    - Re-thinking Minimum Contacts: The Problem of Jurisprudence and Choice of Law in Cyberspace, Program #8 tape #2, 97-1516 (Box 113)
    - Evolutionary IP and the Question of Sovereignty: The Domain Names and Trademarks Issue, Program #9 tape #1, 97-1517 (Box 113)
    - Evolutionary IP and the Question of Sovereignty: The Domain Names and Trademarks Issue, Program #9 tape #2, 97-1517 (Box 113)
    - How Shall the Net Be Governed? Net Governance and the Legal Future of Cyberspace, Program #10 tape #1, 97-1518 (Box 113)
    - How Shall the Net Be Governed? Net Governance and the Legal Future of Cyberspace, Program #10 tape #2, 97-1518 (Box 113)
  - Select Issues in Biomedical Ethics
    - Principles of Medical Ethics and the Duties Deriving from Them, Program #1, 98-1520 (Box 113)
    - Ethical Issues in Genetics and the Human Genome Project, Program #2, 98-1521 (Box 113)
    - Ethical Issues in Genetics and the Human Genome Project, Program #3 -, 98-1522 (Box 113)
    - Ethics in Emergency Medicine, Program #4, 98-1523 (Box 113)
    - Ethics in Emergency Medicine, Part 2: Program #5, 98-1524 (Box 113)
    - Physician-Assisted Suicide: Ethical Issues, Program #6 tape #1, 98-1525 (Box 114)
    - Physician-Assisted Suicide: Ethical Issues, Program #6, 98-1525 (Box 114)
    - Physician-Assisted Suicide: Ethical Issues, Part 2: Program #7 tape #1, 98-1526 (Box 114)
    - Physician-Assisted Suicide: Ethical Issues, Part 2: Program #7, 98-1526 (Box 114)
    - Managed Care: Ethical Issues, Program #8, 98-1527 (Box 114)
    - Ethical Issues in Organ Transplantation and Course Review, Program #9, 98-1528 (Box 114)
  - Stanford Medicine: The HIV Course
    - Molecular Biology of Human Immunodeficiency Virus Type 1, 99-1529 (Box 114)
    - The HIV-1 Pandemia, 99-1530 (Box 114)
    - Laboratory Diagnosis and Quantitation of HIV Infection and AIDS, 99-1531 (Box 114)
    - Immunopathogenesis of HIV Infection, 99-1532 (Box 114)
    - Introduction to Antiretroviral Therapy: Principles and Drugs, 99-1533 (Box 114)
    - Antiretroviral therapy: Prescribing the Medications, 99-1534 (Box 114)
    - Causes for Antiretroviral Therapy to Fail to Control Progression of HIV Infection, 99-1535 (Box 114)
    - Development of Future Antiretroviral Compounds, 99-1536 (Box 115)
    - Opportunistic Infections in AIDS Patients, 99-1537 (Box 115)
    - Primary Care of the HIV-Infected Patient, 99-1538 (Box 115)
    - HIV in Women During Pregnancy, 99-1539 (Box 115)
    - HIV-Related Psychiatric Syndromes, 99-1540 (Box 115)
    - Dermatological Complications in AIDS patients, 99-1541 (Box 115)
    - milestones in the current understanding and treatment of HIV infection, 99-1542 (Box 115)
  - HIV Medicine
    - Introduction and Immune Response against Human Immunodeficiency Virus Infection, 01-1551 (Box 115)
    - Molecular Biology and Viral Dynamics of the Human Immunodeficiency Virus, 01-1552 (Box 115)
    - Laboratory Diagnosis and Quantitation of HIV Infection and AIDS and the HIV Pandemic, 01-1553 (Box 115)
    - Antiretroviral Therapy: Principles and Practice and Common Toxicities and Drug-Drug Interactions Associated with the use of Antiretroviral Toxicities, 01-1554 (Box 115)
    - Metabolic and Fat Distribution Abnormalities Associated with Antiretroviral Therapy and What Does it Mean to Live with HIV Infection? tape #1, 01-1555 (Box 116)
    - Metabolic and Fat Distribution Abnormalities Associated with Antiretroviral Therapy and What Does it Mean to Live with HIV Infection? tape #2, 01-1555 (Box 116)
    - HIV Drug Resistance: Mechanisms and Methods for Detection and Monitoring and Clinical Relevance of HIV Resistance, 01-1556 (Box 116)
    - "New Generation NNRTI's" and "Fusion Inhibitors", 01-1557 (Box 116)
    - AIDS-associated Opportunitistic Infections and AIDS-associated Malignancies, 01-1558 (Box 116)
    - Origins of HIV tape #1, 01-1559 (Box 116)
    - Origins of HIV tape #2, 01-1559 (Box 116)
    - Hepatitis C and HIV Co-infection tape #1, 01-1560 (Box 116)
    - Hepatitis C and HIV Co-infection tape #2, 01-1560 (Box 116)
    - Pediatric AIDS and HIV in Women tape #1, 01-1561 (Box 116)
    - Pediatric AIDS and HIV in Women tape #2, 01-1561 (Box 116)
    - HIV Post-Exposure Prophylaxis and Primary HIV Infection and HIV during Pregnancy and Vertical Transmission tape #1, 01-1562 (Box 116)
    - HIV Post-Exposure Prophylaxis and Primary HIV Infection and HIV during Pregnancy and Vertical Transmission tape #2, 01-1562 (Box 116)
    - Anti-retroviral Therapy: Past, Present and Future, 01-1563 (Box 116)
  - Nobel Perspectives on Ethics in Science
    - A Case History of Data Falsification, 97-1607 (Box 116)
    - A Framework for Analysis, 97-1606 (Box 116)
    - Genetic Frontier: Opportunities and Responsibilities, 97-1609 (Box 117)
    - Lecture #5: Arthur Schawlow, 97-1610 (Box 117)
    - Biotechnology: Biology or Technology, 97-1608 (Box 117)
    - Lecture #6: Herb Abrams, 97-1611 (Box 117)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education
    - Miseducation of the Negro, 97-1612 (Box 117)
    - The Legacy of the Panthers, 97-1613 (Box 117)
    - "Am I Black Enough Fo' Ya?" Issues in Black Identity, Diversity and Community, 97-1614 (Box 117)
    - Sociobiology and Oppression: Sexism, Nationalism & Racism, 97-1615 (Box 117)
    - Race and Justice, 97-1616 (Box 117)
    - Race as a Stress Factor, 97-1617 (Box 117)
    - Mentoring and Manhood Training, 97-1618 (Box 117)
    - Let's Make It: Black Women, Violence and Justice in "Set It Off", 97-1619 (Box 118)
    - Black Germans In Context of "Race" Discourse: 1900 - 1933, 97-1620 (Box 118)
    - After Affirmative Action: On the Why of Black Studies, 97-1633 (Box 119)
    - The Past, Present and Future of Black Studies: What Went Wrong?, 97-1634 (Box 119)
    - Black Studies Challenging Intellectual Hegemony and Racist Science: The Maturation of a Discipline, 97-1635 (Box 119)
    - What About Me, What About You, What About Us: Understanding African-American Existentialists, Allegorialists and Kindness, 98-1636 (Box 119)
    - Black Studies and the Pedagogy of Critical Race Theory, 98-1637 (Box 119)
    - The Why of Black Studies, 98-1638 (Box 119)
    - Why Black Studies?, 98-1639 (Box 119)
    - Harnessing Anger: The Inner Discipline of Athletic Excellence, 98-1650 (Box 122)
    - The Impact of Race and Acculturation on Decision-Making, 98-1651 (Box 122)
    - Multi-America, 98-1652 (Box 122)
    - Jackie Robinson: A Biography, 98-1653 (Box 122)
    - Traditional Healing Methods in the Sea Islands, 99-1654 (Box 122)
    - Reflections on Daughters of the Dust and Black Women Film Makers, 99-1655 (Box 122)
    - Forging New Identities: Africans, Europeans, and American Indians in Early South Carolina, 99-1656 (Box 122)
    - African and African-American Students Partnering for the Development of the Diaspora, 99-1658 (Box 122)
    - Where the Roots Still Show: African Creole Connections in the Language and Culture of the South Carolina Islands, 99-1659 (Box 122)
    - Enactment of a Generation: Global Hip-Hop Youth Culture, 99-1660 (Box 122)
  - A Symposium Honoring the Contributions of Amos Tversky
    - Normative Standards: An Appreciation of the Contribution of Amos Tversky, 97-1628 (Box 118)
    - How Law Constructs Preferences, 97-1629 (Box 118)
    - The Problem of Thinking Too Much (#3), 97-1630 (Box 119)
    - Tversky and Economics: Past and Future Contributions, 97-1631 (Box 119)
    - Tversky: Defender of Rational Choice, 97-1632 (Box 119)
  - Genetic Testing and Breast Cancer: Moral, Legal and Social Issues
    - Introduction: The Genetics of Breast Cancer and Ethical Dilemmas in Genetic Testing and Counseling tape #1, 97-1622 (Box 118)
    - Introduction: The Genetics of Breast Cancer and Ethical Dilemmas in Genetic Testing and Counseling tape #2, 97-1622 (Box 118)
    - The Role of the Biotechnology Industry, 97-1623 (Box 118)
    - Keynote Address by Francis Collins, Program #3, 97-1624 (Box 118)
    - Comparing National Perspectives, Program #4, 97-1625 (Box 118)
    - Voices of People at Risk, Program #5, 97-1626 (Box 118)
    - The Social and Cultural Realities of Predicting Breast Cancer Risk and Where Do We Go From Here? Program #6 tape #1, 97-1627 (Box 118)
    - The Social and Cultural Realities of Predicting Breast Cancer Risk and Where Do We Go From Here? Program #6 tape #2, 97-1627 (Box 118)
  - Human vs. Computer Creativity
    - Chess and Go, Part 1 tape #1, 97-1640/a (Box 119)
    - Chess and Go, Part 1 tape #2, 97-1640/a (Box 119)
    - Chess and Go, Part 2, 97-1640/b (Box 120)
    - Language and Literature, Part 1 tape #1, 97-1641/a (Box 120)
    - Language and Literature, Part 1 tape #2, 97-1641/a (Box 120)
    - Language and Literature, Part 2, 97-1641/b (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 1 tape #1, 97-1642/a (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 1, 97-1642/a (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 2, 97-1642/b (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 3, 97-1642/c (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 4, 97-1642/d (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 5, 97-1642/e (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 6 tape #1, 97-1642/f (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 6, 97-1642/f (Box 120)
    - Music and Computers, Part 7, 97-1642/g (Box 120)
    - Creation of Jokes and Humor tape #1, 97-1643 (Box 120)
    - Creation of Jokes and Humor, 97-1643 (Box 120)
    - The Big Picture, 97-1644/a (Box 121)
    - The Big Picture, 97-1644/b (Box 121)
    - The Big Picture, 97-1644/c (Box 121)
  - Russia at the End of the 20th Century: Culture and Its Horizons in Politics & Society
    - #1: The New Russia Defines Her Past tape #1, 98-1645/a (Box 121)
    - #1: The New Russia Defines Her Past, 98-1645/a (Box 121)
    - The New Russia Defines Her Past, Part 2, 98-1645/b (Box 121)
    - From the Post-Soviet Space to Russia's Place tape #1, 98-1646 (Box 121)
    - From the Post-Soviet Space to Russia's Place, 98-1646 (Box 121)
    - Russia in the Global Order, 98-1647 (Box 121)
    - Emergence of Society and Its Cultures tape #1, 98-1648/a (Box 121)
    - Emergence of Society and Its Cultures, 98-1648/a (Box 121)
    - Emergence of Society and Its Cultures, 98-1648/b (Box 121)
    - New and Improved: Post-Soviet Institutions, Their Meaning and Practice, 98-1649/a (Box 121)
    - New and Improved: Post-Soviet Institutions, Their Meaning and Practice, 98-1649/b (Box 121)
  - African and Afro-American Lecture Series
    - Making Tropical Africa in the Georgia Sea Islands, 99-1657 (Box 122)
  - Women and Health
    - Cardiovascular Health and Disease Prevention in Women, 97-1701 (Box 123)
    - Looking for Love in All the Wrong Places, 97-1702 (Box 123)
    - Integrating Alternative and Conventional Medicine, 97-1703 (Box 123)
    - A Strategy for Early Prevention of Osteoporosis, 97-1704 (Box 123)
    - Providing Quality Health Care for Fat Patients, 97-1705 (Box 123)
    - Delancey Street Foundation: An Educational Model for Recovery from Drug Abuse and Violence, 97-1706 (Box 123)
    - Women's Bone Health, 97-1707 (Box 123)
    - Self Care for Body, Mind and Spirit, 97-1708 (Box 123)
    - Women and Autoimmune Diseases: Introduction to the Immune System, 97-1709 (Box 123)
    - Clinical Aspects of Rheumatoid Arthritis and Systemic Lupus, 97-1710 (Box 123)
    - Innovative Pharmacological Therapies: The Example of DHEA for Systemic Lupus, 97-1711 (Box 124)
    - The Controversy Over Silicone Breast Implants, 97-1712 (Box 124)
    - Future Directions in Research, 97-1713 (Box 124)
    - Management of Female Urinary Incontinence, 97-1714 (Box 124)
    - What's Happening To Me? Controversies Surrounding Hormone Replacement Therapy, 97-1715 (Box 124)
    - Maintaining Midlife Wellness in Women, 97-1716 (Box 124)
    - Women's Reproductive Tract Cancers: News From a Humanist Perspective, 97-1717 (Box 124)
    - Expedition Inspiration: A Journey to the Summit and Survival Sightings: Art and Healing: A Personal Account of My Healing Experience with Ovarian Cancer, 97-1718 (Box 124)
    - The Health and Well-Being of Asian and Pacific Islander Women, 97-1719 (Box 124)
    - Traditional vs. Western View of Female Circumcision, 97-1720 (Box 124)
    - The Scalpel and the Silver Bear: A Navajo Woman Surgeon's Story, 97-1721 (Box 124)
    - Say My Name: Black Women and Health, 97-1722 (Box 125)
    - Mood and Menopause, 97-1723 (Box 125)
    - Working Together: Interdisciplinary Care of the Sexual Trauma Survivor, 97-1724 (Box 125)
    - It's About Life: Issues of Health Access for Young Women of Color, 98-1725 (Box 125)
    - Women Living with HIV: What Health Professionals Need to Know, 98-1726 (Box 125)
    - Culturally Competent Care for Diverse Populations of Women, 98-1727 (Box 125)
    - Premenstrual Syndrome: Diagnosis, Pathophysiology and Treatment, 98-1728 (Box 125)
    - Sharing the Journey: Women with Breast Cancer Speak from the Heart, 98-1729 (Box 125)
    - The Residency Experience of African-American Female General Surgeons, 98-1730 (Box 125)
    - The Art and Issues of Dying: The Perspective of a Physician/Filmmaker, 98-1731 (Box 125)